

### **ALDI ALFIANDI**

(Birth Name: Dang Aldi Haediar Ali Alfiandi Albar)
Website Programmer, IT Support Role, UI/UX Designer, Coding Educator, Office Administrator
Male | He/Him | 23 y.o. | August 27th, 2000, | Straight/Heterosexual | Married | Sukabumi, West Java, Indonesia
aldialfiandi2708@gmail.com | +62-851-7444-8002 | https://github.com/lev10sa | https://lev10sa.github.io

## **PROFILE**

### **SUMMARY**

I started my career in 2019 and I have gained experience in full-stack website development, IT support, office administration, and anything related to these fields. I am adaptable to any situation and have a proven record of providing solutions, solving various problems, following instructions, fulfilling client requests, and delivering client satisfaction. I am moderately fluent in both English and Indonesian Languages. I am an initiative-taking learner who thrives on new challenges and purposeful endeavors. I consistently bring loyalty, dignity, integrity, trustworthiness, effort, and dedication to achieving goals. I used to work on website development with JavaScript and PHP.

### **EXPERIENCE**

#### PT. SOLUSI EDUKASI GEMILANG

(Company/Corporate)
March 2023 – Present (Currently Working)
IT Support Role (Remote/WFA)
Salary: \$. 350,00 per month

Working hours: max. 40 hours per week and max. 8 hours per day

• Supporting sales, purchasing, and digital marketing team on IT related matters

### **LEV10CODE**

(Freelance/Self-Employment)
September 2022 – Present (Currently Working)
Coding Educator (Remote/WFA)
Average earnings: Rp. 1,000.000,00 to Rp. 1.50

Average earnings: Rp. 1,000.000,00 to Rp. 1.500.000,00 per month Working hours: 2 days per week (on weekend) and max. 4 hours per day

Tutoring about Website Programming from basic to intermediate

### LEV10SA

(Freelance/Self-Employment)
August 2019 – Present (Currently Working)
Full-stack Website Developer (Remote/WFA)
Average earnings: Rp. 1.500.000,00 to Rp. 4.000.000,00 per month
Working hours: flexible, deadline based

- Developing a full-stack website with MERN or LAMP Stack
- Project maintenance and troubleshooting

# DINAS KOMUNIKASI DAN INFORMATIKA KOTA SUKABUMI

(Government/Agency)
April 2018 – August 2018
Office Administrator Intern (Onsite/WFO)
Working hours: max. 40 hours per week and max. 8 hours per day

Managing office administration related matters

### **EDUCATION**

### **SMK ISLAM PENGUJI SUKABUMI**

(Vocational School) Year of 2016 to 2019 (Graduated) Class of Software Engineer

## **EXPERTISE**

### HARD SKILLS

- Code Editor and IDE: Visual Studio Code, Sublime Text, Notepad++, Nano, Vim, Android Studio, NetBeans
- Programming Language: JavaScript, PHP, Java, Kotlin
- Database: MySQL, MongoDB, Supabase
- Markup and Styling: HTML, XML, CSS
- Framework and Library: Laravel, ReactJS, React Native, NextJS, ExpressJS, AstroJS, Materializecss, Daisy UI
- Tech Stack: MERN, SEAN, LAMP
- Office Suite: Microsoft Office/Microsoft 365 (Word, Excel, PowerPoint, Access, SharePoint), Adobe Acrobat Reader (PDF)
- Version Control and Operating System: Git, Linux (Ubuntu, Debian, Kali), Windows Subsystem for Linux (WSL), Windows PowerShell

## **SOFT SKILLS**

Attractive, communicative, adaptive, creative, innovative, observative, cooperative, collaborative, leadership, teamworking, problem solving, critical thinking, time managing, deep learning.